ILGWU 4x5 Negatives of Photographs 5780 P N45
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series Local 22, 1922
  - High Delegate 37 West 28th Street, General Manager to the Joint Board in Los Angeles, 12/15/50, 1950 (Box 29, Folder 56)
  - Marda Springer farewell luncheon, McAlpin, 8/9/51, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 57)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 58)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 59)
  - Abstraction (Box 29, Folder 60)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 61)
  - Meeting membership Manhattan Center Zimmerman speaking, 12/8/51, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 62)
  - Book for new members, Due book, November 1951 (Box 29, Folder 63)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 64)
  - Zimmerman funeral (Box 29, Folder 65)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 66)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 67)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 68)
  - Spanish labor leaders with members (Box 29, Folder 69)
  - Zimmerman, Sasha (Box 29, Folder 70)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 71)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 72)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 73)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 74)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 75)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 76)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 77)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 78)
  - Local 22 A- G (item: N45) (Box 29, Folder 79)
  - Education Conference Zimmerman and Mitdel, 5/23/46, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 80)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 81)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt Jr. (Box 29, Folder 82)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 83)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 84)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 85)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 86)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 87)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 88)
  - Christmas party, 1950 (Box 29, Folder 89)
  - Luncheon for Nahama leaving for Latin American countries as a guest of the State Department, 7/31/59, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 90)
  - Elections for Local and Convention delegates, 1/21/59, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 91)
  - Elections, Zimmerman votes, 2/19/59 (Box 29, Folder 92)
  - Fashion Institute graduation, 6/8/59, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 93)
  - Installation, Harry Rubinstein, 3/11/59, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 94)
  - Israel Breslow and Zimmerman, 8/13/58, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 95)
  - Golden Age Program retired members post retirement program with Jewish Alliance Jewish Labor Committee, etc., 4/3/57, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 96)
  - Local 22 Dressmakers Liberal Party club starts drive to raise tax exemptions from the bottom up, 4/13/54, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 97)
  - New Business agent Louise Delgado with Sabby Nehama and Zimmerman, 3/22/57, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 98)
  - Meeting at Manhattan Center, Zimmerman gets award from National Urban League Director Lester B. Granger (Box 29, Folder 99)
  - Diplomat Hotel Senator Lehman and Zimmerman, 10/29/52, 1952 (Box 29, Folder 100)
  - Political, Halley for Mayor with Joe Nagler speaking at 38st and Broadway, 10/20/53, 1953 (Box 29, Folder 101)
- Series Children of Local 22
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 102)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 103)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 104)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 105)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 106)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 107)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 108)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 109)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 110)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 111)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 112)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 113)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 114)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 115)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 116)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 117)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 118)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 119)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 120)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 121)
- Series Local 23
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 122)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 123)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 124)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 125)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 126)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 127)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 128)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 129)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 130)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 131)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 132)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 133)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 134)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 135)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 136)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 137)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 138)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 139)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 140)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 141)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 142)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 143)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 144)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 145)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 146)
  - Chinese members at Unity, 6/22/58, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 147)
  - New manager Shelly Appleton says farewell to old manager Louis Riess with Isidore Nagler in center (Box 29, Folder 148)
  - Film strip, 8/8/51, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 149)
  - Unity House weekend outing, 6/22/57, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 150)
  - Story Industry, 2/1959 (Box 29, Folder 151)
  - Appleton installed by Nagler, 3/19/59 (Box 29, Folder 152)
  - New manager and old Shelly Appleton, Isidore Nagler and Louis Reiss, 12/1958 (Box 29, Folder 153)
  - Contract ratified Hotel Diplomat Nagler speaking with Louis Reiss, 4/17/58, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 154)
  - Sportswear agreement Cloak Joint Board, 5/12/54, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 155)
  - Members hear report agreement on new agreement by Louis Reiss on right Aaron Pankin, 7/14/53, 1953 (Box 29, Folder 156)
  - Installation by Nagler, 3/10/53, 1953 (Box 29, Folder 157)
  - Story, 2/1959 (Box 29, Folder 158)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 159)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 160)
  - Modern shop scene, Business agents, Price settlement, Office at work, Dues paying, Retirement interview and Film Strip, 7/20/51, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 161)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 162)
  - Annual dance with Louis Reiss in the center of crowd, 2/25/50, 1950 (Box 29, Folder 163)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 164)
  - Annual Dance, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 165)
  - Executive Board, 8/1951 (Box 29, Folder 166)
  - Christmas Dinner at Boys club, 12/1950 (Box 29, Folder 167)
  - First retirement check to Local 23 members (Box 29, Folder 168)
  - George Rubin and Louis Reiss at Unity, 6/29/51, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 169)
  - Aaron Pankin elected Assistant Manager and Louis Reiss, 1/30/58, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 170)
  - Contract signing, 5/8/58, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 171)
  - Christmas party at Manhattan Center with Stulberg, Martin Cohen, etc. (Box 29, Folder 172)
  - Stulberg attends, 11/1958 (Box 29, Folder 173)
  - New manager at work- Appleton, 1/21/59, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 174)
  - Official opening of new headquarters at 275 7th Avenue 10th floor, 1/18/60, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 175)
  - New headquarters, 1/26/60, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 176)
- Series Local 25, 1925
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 177)
  - Chair luncheon at Hotel Astor with Judy Stulberg, 11/24/51, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 178)
  - Kreindler Luncheon (Box 29, Folder 179)
  - Chairlady Luncheon with Judy Stulberg and C. Kreindler (Box 29, Folder 180)
  - Annual Luncheon at Astor Hotel, 11/1950 (Box 29, Folder 181)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 182)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 183)
  - Weekend at Unity, 6/23-25/50, 1950 (Box 29, Folder 184)
  - Installation Joseph DAmaro age 7 congratulates Kreindler at Installation, 4/2/53, 1953 (Box 29, Folder 185)
  - Installation and new agreement ratification meet Manhattan Center installed by Stulberg, 4/2/53, 1953 (Box 29, Folder 186)
  - Contract renewal meet at Manhattan Center (Box 29, Folder 187)
  - Heads (Box 29, Folder 188)
  - Ben Leibowitz retiree wished well Carrie Franco Local 25 president and Kreindler manager, 1/7/53, 1953 (Box 29, Folder 189)
  - New wage increase Manhattan Center with crowd and Kreindler, 12/13/50, 1950 (Box 29, Folder 190)
  - Kreindler TV to Unity, 6/24/48, 1948 (Box 29, Folder 191)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 192)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 193)
  - Kreindler, 11/20/48, 1948 (Box 29, Folder 194)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 195)
  - Ratifies agreement, 3/11/59, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 196)
  - Official opening of new headquarters 275 7th Avenue 11th floor, 1/18/60, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 197)
  - Cumberland MD. (Box 29, Folder 198)
- Series Local 30, 1930
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 199)
  - Dinner honoring Nicholas Mastroto Chief of Executive Board and founder of Local 30, 4/30/58, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 200)
  - Elections at Manhattan Center, 5/17/59, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 201)
- Series Local 32
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 202)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 203)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 204)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 205)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 206)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 207)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 208)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 209)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 210)
  - Executive Board (Box 29, Folder 211)
  - Installation by Stulberg, Shiffman, 4/14/53, 1953 (Box 29, Folder 212)
  - Party, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 213)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 214)
  - Staff Conference, 1/29/53, 1953 (Box 29, Folder 215)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 216)
  - 20 Anniversary Luncheon at Commodore Hotel with Melvin Kleeblatt, Jed Sylbert, Snyder, Dubinsky, Max Ladenheim and Lillian Daniels, 2/20/54, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 217)
  - Manhattan Center Annual, Moss Show and Dance with new manager Max Goldenberg, Stulberg, Antonini and Snyder, 12/12/58, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 218)
  - 20th Anniversary meeting and entertainment at the Commodore Hotel with M. Falikman and Louis Stulberg. 2/12/54, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 219)
  - Installation Max Goldenberg new manager, 2/24/56, 1956 (Box 29, Folder 220)
  - Contract signing with Piorette bros. firm with W. Danial, Max Goldenberg, Abe Dodger and Milard L. Midonick (Box 29, Folder 221)
  - Contract signing with Simone Co. Inc. with Goldenberg, Morris Glusheim, Millard L. Midonick and Aaron Shaffer, 11/18/59, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 222)
  - Ratification meeting at Roosevelt Hotel Max Goldenberg getting approval for the new contract, 1/5/60, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 223)
- Series Local 35, 1935
  - 3 generations of pressers William (73), Harry (52) and Sydney (26) Gerstein, 5/6/57, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 224)
  - Register Pickets 34th 7th Avenue (Box 29, Folder 225)
  - Anita Coat Corporation gives party for Harry Cooperman going to Israel, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 226)
    Chairman local 35 shakes hands with employer Muriel Paley and Business Agent Abe Belson also Harry Finkel and Harry Levenson, July 19, 1951
  - Retirement luncheon with Oscar Stein (74), Breslav, Dubrow (70) and Mike Cooperman, 12/5/51, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 227)
  - Installation by Dubinsky at Hotel New Yorker, 3/17/53, 1953 (Box 29, Folder 228)
  - Testimonial dinner to Edward Weisman, shakes hands with George Breslow, 2/6/54, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 229)
  - Voting at Hotel Diplomat (Box 29, Folder 230)
  - Heads of members, 10/22/57, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 231)
  - Morris Kovler elected manager unanimously, 9/19/57 (Box 29, Folder 232)
  - Political active members, 10/9/57, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 233)
  - Pressers helps to fill out PPR forms at local, CBS Fashions 325 West 37th Street with Isidore Linger, Marvin Bargrassen, Irving Goldstein in shop, Hyman Males, Isidore Samter and C. Bernstein, 6/25/57, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 234)
  - Membership meeting appointment of assistant manager, 5/15/57, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 235)
  - Member meet, 4/21/58, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 236)
  - Member meet at Hotel Diplomat, 8/7/58, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 237)
  - Political Group,, Long Island, 7/19/58 (Box 29, Folder 238)
  - Installation by Dubinsky at Hotel Diplomat, 3/26/59, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 239)
  - Political action committee, 7/15/58, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 240)
  - Membership Committee Conference, 8/7/58, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 241)
  - Younger members, 1/29/58, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 242)
  - Pressers anti-retirees age 78 to 69, 1/29/58, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 243)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 244)
  - April 30, 1949. (Box 29, Folder 245)
  - Manager and staff (Box 29, Folder 246)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 247)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 248)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 249)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 250)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 251)
  - Elections at Hotel Diplomat, 3/11 (Box 29, Folder 252)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 253)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 254)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 255)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 256)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 257)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 258)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 259)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 260)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 261)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 262)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 263)
  - Minimum wage call for 125 % increase, 4/7/54, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 264)
  - Local elections, 1/1959 (Box 29, Folder 265)
- Series Local 38
  - Mrs. Roosevelt speaks to Membership with Isidore Sorkin manager on her recent trip to Russia, 1/29/58, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 266)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 267)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 268)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 269)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 270)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 271)
  - Election Nominations, 2/1950 (Box 29, Folder 272)
  - Jean Muir (Box 29, Folder 273)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 274)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 275)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 276)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 277)
  - Hand Craft class (Box 29, Folder 278)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 279)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 280)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 281)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 282)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 283)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 284)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 285)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 286)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 287)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 288)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 289)
  - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 290)
  - Social Dancing Class instructor Joe Sharkey, 2/5/51, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 291)
  - Meeting Halley speaking for Mayor, 10/14/53, 1953 (Box 29, Folder 292)
  - Executive Board and delegates to Convention, 4/13/59, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 293)
  - Madame Pandet speaking to members with Frank Rosenfarb, 12/1/53, 1953 (Box 29, Folder 294)
  - Elections at Headquarters, 3/11/53, 1953 (Box 29, Folder 295)
  - Election James Waxler post-election, 1/14/53, 1953 (Box 29, Folder 296)
- Series Local 40
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Nordray Belt Company 630 Broadway fire drill in progress, 6/10/58, 1958 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Arts and Crafts (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Dues (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Opening of a new hotel on 49 West 37th Street with Dubinsky, Umhey, Z. Freidman and crowd, 11/15/51, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Retirees 9 members, DUBINSKY gets belt as gift from retirees, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    Inauguration of Retirement benefit fund, Speakers Henry Schwartz Mgr., Herbert Novick Exec. Dr., Dr. Betassor, Elias Lieberman attorney, Harry Greenberg Vice President Manager Local 91 and DUBINSKY, February 16, 1954
  - Henry Schwartz reporting and member at Hotel Diplomat, seated is Angelo Ciccotto local 40 Chairman (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - 40 Portrait Spanish Dressmaker beauty contest winner Genovene Cabello at Albrite Belt Corporation, 315 West 35th Street (Box 30, Folder 23)
- Series Local 48
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Italian Ambassador gets check for Italian Red Cross, 300 children adopted, June 26 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - DUBINSKY installed (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Testimonial to Ed Molisani, 9/14/49 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - Installation, DUBINSKY congratulates Comminali and Molisoni, 2/50, 1950 (Box 30, Folder 41)
  - E. Molisani and Mrs., and Count Sforza, 10/6/49, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 42)
  - Molisani birthday at Astor Hotel 70 years old, 4/6/51, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 43)
  - Gives 13,000 to complete construction of Villagia del Fanciullo, July 11, 1950 (Box 30, Folder 44)
  - Gives 2,000 to Italian American Labor Council, 7/18/50, 1950 (Box 30, Folder 45)
  - Dinner by Executive Board For Molisani return from Italy, Pagliares restaurant on 66 East 11th Street, 8/15/51, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 46)
  - Executive Board Dinner, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 47)
  - Election, 2/2/50, 1950 (Box 30, Folder 48)
  - Gives 6,000, 3/20/52, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 49)
  - February 19, 1953. (Box 30, Folder 50)
  - 75th Birthday celebration for E. Molisani at Waldorf Astoria (Box 30, Folder 51)
  - Howard Molisani elected Manager of 48 meeting at Labor Temple 14th Street and 2nd Avenue, 7/26/55, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 52)
  - Election Edward Molisani votes at Headquarters, 2/7/56, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 53)
  - At Unity House weekend outing, 6/22/57, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 54)
  - Aid Italian Children Boystown, 4/8/54, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 55)
  - Annual Dance, 10/51, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 56)
  - Unity House, 6/11/54, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 57)
  - Installation at Labor Temple, 2/28/56, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 58)
  - Post humous award to E. Molisani by Italian Governor, 4/2/57, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 59)
  - Send off dinner for Molisani leaving for Italy, 4/3057, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 60)
  - Unveiling of E. Molisani portrait and check for Boystown presented by Howard Molisani, John Carrol, 4/1/55, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 61)
  - Installation, 3/59, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 62)
  - Election at Headquarters, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 63)
  - Howard Molisani in Rome, Italy (Box 30, Folder 64)
- Series Local 60
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 65)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 66)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 67)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 68)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 69)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 70)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 71)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 72)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 73)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 74)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 75)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 76)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 77)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 78)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 79)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 80)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 81)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 82)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 83)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 84)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 85)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 86)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 87)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 88)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 89)
  - Pressers donate 3,500, 11/11/45, 1945 (Box 30, Folder 90)
  - Bernard Lurye greeted by Local 60 officers and workers, 5/10/54, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 91)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 92)
  - Elections, voting at Headquarters, 2/3/59, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 93)
  - Executive Board Pointing to new Manager Bill Schwartz, 12/15/59, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 94)
  - Max Cohen funeral, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 95)
  - At pressers Local 89 Ball, 11/21/52, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 96)
  - DUBINSKY receives bronze sculpture of himself on his birthday, Jack Spitzer and Board, 2/21/52, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 97)
  - Max Cohen Funeral, 5/25/50, 1950 (Box 30, Folder 98)
  - Dress Joint Board New chairman (Box 30, Folder 99)
  - William Schwartz Presser is elected to Business Agent, 2/50, 1950 (Box 30, Folder 100)
  - Business Agent Max Schecter retires (Box 30, Folder 101)
  - Meeting of Local 60 on Health Program for members at Hotel Diplomat (Box 30, Folder 102)
  - Dinner for DUBINSKY, 4/49, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 103)
  - Workman Circle Branch 761E Installation Chair Of Local Joel Manist and Executive Chair of Local William. Schwartz (Box 30, Folder 104)
  - Convention booklet, 5/53, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 105)
  - Election objection committee, 1/30/53, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 106)
  - Elections, 2/3/53, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 107)
  - Gives blood to Red Cross Blood Bank 40th Street 5th and 6th Avenue for Korea, 2/5/52, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 108)
  - Installation by Antonini at Diplomat Hotel, 2/24/53, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 109)
  - Branch B meeting with Sam Cohen and Max Weisen pressing department gives 200 for Histadrute, Louie Livine, Marty Kufman and Jack Spitzer, 1/10/52, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 110)
  - Installation at Diplomat Hotel, 2/27/52, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 111)
  - Dress pressers (Box 30, Folder 112)
  - Jack Spitzer, etc. (Box 30, Folder 113)
  - Dress pressers Branch, 601 8th Avenue, 10/13/58, 1958 (Box 30, Folder 114)
  - Meeting Halley for Mayor, 10/12/53, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 115)
  - Bill Schwartz Manager is congratulated, 12/3/59, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 116)
  - Installation, Schwartz and DUBINSKY, 2/26/59, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 117)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 118)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 119)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 120)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 121)
  - Drive to organize Dress Shipping Union to be called Local 60 A, 9/21/53, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 122)
  - Dress shipping clerks distribute leaflets at 1400 Broadway at noon, 10/7/53, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 123)
  - Visit United Nations gives honorary union card to Ralph Bunche, 1/15/55, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 124)
  - Samuel Mack retires, 9/1/58, 1958 (Box 30, Folder 125)
  - Contract signing, April 4, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 126)
  - Contract signing with Dress Industry, 3/31/54, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 127)
  - Membership drive meeting guest speakers William Walpert, August Classins and Jack Spitzer, 12/7/53, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 128)
  - Chorus at Local 60A at ILG exhibit, 1710 Broadway, 4/22/57, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 129)
  - Chorus at Spring Art Show, 4/11- 28/55, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 130)
  - March 21, 1955. (Box 30, Folder 131)
  - Installation, Manhattan Center, 3/6/56, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 132)
- Series Local 62
  - Protestors (Box 30, Folder 133)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 134)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 135)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 136)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 137)
  - Cross country tour members and manager M. Shoenwald with a map of the country, 2/2/60, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 138)
  - Skit at Party at 62 headquarters, 5/52, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 139)
  - At Unity 50th Anniversary of Local, 9/11 -13/59, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 140)
  - Convention Delegate, 8/4/59, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 141)
  - Millicent Porter Convention Delegate, 8/4/59, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 142)
  - Meeting and distribution of union label and literature at Lanes and Saks department store on 34th street, 12/3/59, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 143)
  - Fire victims 6 memorial meet at Roosevelt Auditorium on 873 Broadway, 3/24/58, 1958 (Box 30, Folder 144)
  - Educational lecture, 1/59, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 145)
  - Vacation checks, 6/4/57, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 146)
  - Unity house meet on rent control with Ralph Morhard Deputy rent control committee of New York State, 1/29/59, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 147)
  - Voice of America Broadcast on 250 West 57th Street, 1/20/58, 1958 (Box 30, Folder 148)
  - Jamie Togs 588 Broadway, Vacation checks and Schoenwald, 6/9/58, 1958 (Box 30, Folder 149)
  - Vacation checks, June 3, 1958 (Box 30, Folder 150)
  - Schoenwald and Commissioner Fire Department, Triangle survivor and monarch, 4/14/58, 1958 (Box 30, Folder 151)
  - Ratifying new agreement at Roosevelt Hotel, 7/29/58, 1958 (Box 30, Folder 152)
  - Graduates qualified chairladies show their certificates in center is Mayor M. Schoenwald, 4/30/57, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 153)
  - Manager Mat Schoenwald points to employed PPR poster, 7/29/57, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 154)
  - Renews contract signing, 6/7/56, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 155)
  - Members meet election of new officers in Roosevelt Auditorium, 1/12/56, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 156)
  - Installation at Roosevelt Auditorium, 3/6/50, 1950 (Box 30, Folder 157)
  - Workers receive vacation checks, 6/2/54, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 158)
  - Renewal of contract with Underwear association, 9/28/58, 1958 (Box 30, Folder 159)
  - Unknown (Box 30, Folder 160)